# Saint Paul Bassanaga VI



saintbassanaga01@gmail.com



+237652943257



linkedin.com/in/saintpaulbassanaga



https://saintbassanaga.github.io/saintbassanagae/

### Summary

I am recently certified as Full Stack Software Engineer by the ALX-Africa School of Engineering in partnership with the Holberton Institute of Computer Science. I want to develop my experience with branches like DevOps and technologies like blockchain.

Likewise, I am listening to any internship offer or junior developer position (remote or hybrid). Also, I am open to any relocation needs.

As I need to become a better Engineer, I am more attuned to an associate position where I can learn from my mentor and, at the same time, participate in improving the team.

### **Experience**



#### olx Student Software Engineer

alx\_africa

May 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

The African Leadership X Accelerator is an African Leadership Group subsidiary company, in its mission of technologies growth in Africa has designed a Software Engineering curriculum that lasts 12 months. The curriculum is divided into two different parts: 9 months of Foundations course and 3 months of short specialization.

## ဟု Software Engineer

Upwork

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)

As freelance software engineers, it is up to us to apply for a fixed-term job or an hourly contract:

Which implies:

- competitiveness
- the desire to do well
- The speed of delivery
- Expertise

#### **Brand Ambassador**

MTN

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017 (4 months)

As Ambassadors of the MTN Mobile Money brand, it was a question for us to popularize the mobile money system in Cameroon by approaching potential customers for:

- Create new Mobile Money accounts
- Update suspended accounts
- Interest customers to use it to have a mobile money account

#### **Education**

### INSTITUT SUPERIEUR MATAMFEN

Associate's Degree, Computer Software Engineering En cours de BTS

### **Udacity**

**AWS Machine Learning Foundations Course** 

Jan 2023 - May 2023

AWS DeepRacer is an integrated learning system for users of all levels to learn, explore reinforcement learning, and experiment and build autonomous driving applications.

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Python Programming Foundations** Udacity HHCPFLKS
- in Les fondements de la programmation Orientee Objet LinkedIn
- in Les fondements de la programmation LinkedIn

#### **Skills**

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Oriented Object Design • C (Programming Language) • Linux • JavaScript • Java • Introduction to Machine Learning • Reinforcement Learning • Learning Model • Client Relations